OLGA EMILEVNA

linkedin.com/in/olga-kuldavletova-380726a7/ · Instagram.com/oemilevna · behance.net/oemilevna · oemilevna@yandex.ru



Research in neuroscience & graphics. Born in 1991 in Petrozavodsk, Russia.

Member and permanent resident of artist association Labo des arts. Working as a researcher and teacher at the University of Caen.

Current location: Caen, France.

EXPÉRIENCE

2009 - PRESENT

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, ILLUSTRATOR

Self-employed

MARCH 2015 - JUNE 2015

ANIMATION TEACHER, 2D ANIMATION COURSE

Courses on History of animation and Adobe Flash animation basics

2011 - 2014

ART TEACHER, MUSEUM OF FINE ARTS, PETROZAVODSK

Art workshops for groups of children; multiple techniques

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020

PHD FELLOWSHIP, NORMANDY UNIVERSITY OF CAEN

Laboratory COMETE: Multisensory integration and plasticity of orientation related reflexes.

2009 - 2015

BACHELOR'S AND MASTER'S DEGREES IN COMPUTER SCIENCES,

PETROZAVODSK STATE UNIVERSITY

After: traineeship in research in human physiology and neuroscience.

2013

PAUL POLAKOV'S STUDIO

Watercolor painting and pencil graphics

2014

2D ANIMATION COURSE

An intensive animation course, creation of an author animation project

SKILLS

- 2D animation
- Graphic design

- Printmaking; etching
- Vector illustration

GRAPHIC SOFTWARE

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe AfterEffects
- Adobe Premier

ETCHING TECHNIQUES

- Eau-forte
- Mezzotinte
- Aquatinte
- Soft-ground etching
- Drypoint
- Linocut

EXHIBITIONS

- April 2015 Paul Polakov's Student exhibition, Petrozavodsk (watercolor)
- April 2018 Exhibition of proverbs an anthropology project of NPO VOVA, Caen (graphic design; vector illustration)
- May 2018 Art.Lastochka I, Petrozavodsk (etching)
- May 2019 Art.Lastochka II, Petrozavodsk (etching)
- June 2019 "Mujeres ilustradoras en formato pequeno II", Berlin (etching)
- February 2021 Exhibition Labo des arts, 5 artists, Caen (etching, printing)
- 2016 2019 Posters exposed at science conferences in Pecs (Hungary), Le Havre, Rouen, Caen (France) and at The Festival of Science 2018 in Caen

ANIMATION FILMS

- 2014 A short animation film based on "A wish to be a red indian" by F. Kafka. The film was projected on a big screen in the Petrozavodsk State University, Saint-Petersburg State University, Cultura Club, Saint-Petersburg (the international event dedicated to Kafka) and at the literary event in Vienna.
- A short film for a bookshop in Saint-Petersburg, Russia. The film was projected on a big screen in the Petrozavodsk State University, and in the WordOrder (Poryadok Slov) in Saint-Petersburg.